krystalskitsch.com 2019-05-18

# Privacy Policy and Disclosures » Sunny Sweet Days

This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by Sunny Sweet Days. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect when you use “Services”, or when you otherwise interact with us.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the “Last Updated” date at the top of this policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as by adding a statement to our website or by sending you a notification). We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy whenever you access the Services or otherwise interact with us to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

#### Collection of Information

Information You Provide to Us: We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you create an account, participate in any interactive features of the Services, subscribe to a newsletter or email list, participate in an event, survey, contest or promotion, make a purchase, communicate with us via third-party social media sites, request customer support or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect include your name, email address, password, postal address, phone number, gender, date of birth, occupation, employer information, photo, payment information (such as your credit or debit card and billing address), preference or interest data, and any other information you choose to provide.

If you provide an email address to invite a friend to participate in the Services, we will collect that email address and use it to send your friend such an invitation.

Information We Collect Automatically: When you access or use our Services, we may automatically collect information about you, including:

Log Information: We collect log information about your use of the Services, including your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, web request, access times, pages viewed, web browser, links clicked and the page you visited before navigating to the Services.

Mobile Device Information: We collect information about the mobile device you use to access our Services, including the hardware model, operating system, and version, unique device identifiers, mobile network information and information about your use of our mobile applications.

Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies: We and our service providers use various technologies to collect information, including cookies and web beacons.

Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us improve our Services and your experience, see which areas and features of our Services are popular, and count visits. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our Services or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits, and understand usage and campaign effectiveness. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see “Your Choices” below.

Information We Collect From Other Sources: We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Services. For example, if you create or log into your account through a third-party social media site, we will have access to certain information from that site, such as your name, account information and friends lists, in accordance with the authorization procedures determined by such social media site; we may also collect information about you when you post content to our pages/feeds on third-party social media sites.

#### Use of Information

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to:

  * Provide, maintain, improve and promote our products and services;
  * Provide and deliver the information, products and services you request, process transactions and send you related information, including confirmations and receipts;
  * Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
  * Respond to your comments, questions and requests, and provide customer service;
  * Communicate with you about products, services, surveys, offers, promotions,rewards and events offered by Company and others, and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you;
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services;
  * Personalize and improve the Services and provide advertisements, content or features that match user profiles or interests;
  * Facilitate contests, sweepstakes and promotions, and process and deliver entries and rewards;
  * Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; and
  * Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.

We are based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries.

#### Sharing of Information

We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy:

  * With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work or perform services on our behalf;
  * When you participate in the interactive areas of our Services, certain information you provide may be displayed to other users, such as your name, photo, comments and other information you choose to provide;
  * In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process;
  * If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies or to protect the rights, property and safety of Company or others;
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company; and
  * With your consent or at your direction.

#### Social Sharing Features

The Services may offer social sharing features and other integrated tools (such as the Facebook “Like” button), which let you share actions you take on our Services with other media, and vice versa. Your use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the entity that provides the social sharing feature. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the entities that provide these features.

#### Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others

We may allow others to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and to provide analytics services. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by Company and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Services and other websites and better understand your online activity. For more information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes by companies that participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance, please visit www.aboutads.info/choices.

 **Display Ads**

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use cookies, as noted above.

 **Retargeting  Ads**

From time to time, the Website may engage in remarketing efforts with third-party companies, such as Google, Facebook, or Instagram, in order to market the Website. These companies use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Website.

 **Affiliate Program Participation**

The Website may engage in affiliate marketing, which is done by embedding tracking links into the Website. If you click on a link for an affiliate partnership, a cookie will be placed on your browser to track any sales for purposes of commissions.

Sunny Sweet Days is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and links to Amazon.com.  As part of this Amazon Associates program, the Website will post customized links, provided by Amazon, to track the referrals to their website. This program utilizes cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

#### Security

Company takes reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

#### Your Choices

Account Information: You may review, correct or modify information maintained in your online account at any time by logging into your account and updating your profile information or by emailing us at hello@sunnysweetdays.com. If you wish to delete or deactivate your account, please email us athello@sunnysweetdays.com, but note that some information you provide through the Services may continue to be accessible (e.g., comments you submit through the Services) and that we may continue to store information about you as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time.

#### Cookies

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability or functionality of our Services

#### Promotional Communications

You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from us by following the instructions in those communications or by sending an email to hello@sunnysweetdays.com. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations.

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at hello@sunnysweetdays.com.

## COOKIE POLICY

We use cookies on our sites (www.sunnysweetdays.com and the subdomains associated with (www.sunnysweetdays.com) (“our site”) for a number of purposes. They help us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allow us to improve our site. By continuing to browse the site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies. A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive.

#### We use the following cookies:

 **Strictly necessary cookies**. These are cookies that are required for the operation of our website. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our website, use a shopping cart or make use of the e-billing services.

 **Analytical/performance cookies**. They allow us to recognize and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users find what they are looking for easily.

 **Functionality cookies**. These are used to recognize you when you return to our website. This enables us to personalize our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).

 **Targeting cookies**. These cookies record your visit to our website, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We will use this information to make our website and the advertising displayed on it more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties for this purpose.

You can find more information about the individual cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them below.

  * First-party (IT Governance Ltd) cookies: This website will set some cookies that are essential for the website to operate correctly. These cookies, none of which capture personally identifiable information, are as follows: 
    * Visitor ID–this cookie is a numeric value that identifies unique visitors and provides coherence and consistency to a site visit;
    * Page Number–this cookie identifies the page you are on;
    * Session ID–this cookie identifies your website session;
    * Test–this cookie checks whether or not your browser supports cookies;
    * Order–this cookie ensures that your shopping basket works correctly.
  * Third-party cookies- Our websites will set several types of third-party cookie, and we do not control the operation of any of them. The third-party cookies which may be set include:
    * Google Analytics–we use Google Analytics to collect data about website usage. This data does not include personally identifiable information. You can view the Google Privacy Policy here: [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/](https://www.dropbox.com/referrer_cleansing_redirect?hmac=U5U%2BDeTdTMdVPAtjONYExQaHyiJW4wIQo82Yacv0ICY%3D&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.google.com%2Fpolicies%2Fprivacy%2F).
    * Social Warfare–the AddThis cookie is used when you use the ShareThis service on our website to share a link with LinkedIn, Facebook, Twitter, etc. You can read the AddThis Privacy Policy here: https://warfareplugins.com/privacy-policy/
    * Facebook Pixels–we use Facebook Pixels to retarget website users for Facebook ads. This means that if you browse our website, you’re more likely to see our Facebook ads. You can view the Privacy Policy here: [https://www.facebook.com/policy.php](https://www.dropbox.com/referrer_cleansing_redirect?hmac=75VP0C%2BiKj0KELSHJqNnGuSHrZAJIokozfRXJYpmOeM%3D&url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Fpolicy.php)
    * CommentLuv–we use CommentLuv to give blog commenters the option to include a link to one of their recent blog posts with their comment. This data improves the users experience. You can opt out of using CommentLuv when posting your comments. For more information on this privacy policy contact the developer here: [https://wordpress.org/plugins/commentluv/](https://www.dropbox.com/referrer_cleansing_redirect?hmac=M4DspHUDocrvPuezU%2Bfc6pDXjLaSfmezS0B4%2BhhBCEg%3D&url=https%3A%2F%2Fwordpress.org%2Fplugins%2Fcommentluv%2F)
    * Leadpages–we use Leadpages to collect names and email addresses when offering upgraded content in blog posts. This gives us the opportunity to continue to send out content to those people who signed up. This is always a double opt-in option. You can find Leadpages Privacy Policy here: https://[www.leadpages.net/privacy.](https://www.dropbox.com/referrer_cleansing_redirect?hmac=FEP2zfGbJJo04%2FmaWLUk%2BQY4T4WjJuUdDdG%2FUZCJXTU%3D&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.leadpages.net%2Fprivacy)
    * Askimet–we use Askimet to block spam comments. It’s a plug-in that blocks suspicious comments (including suspicious IP addresses) so that we don’t have to spend huge chunks of time deleting spam comments. You can view their terms of service right here: [https://akismet.com/tos/](https://www.dropbox.com/referrer_cleansing_redirect?hmac=hSwud9zLDqrBHtRnGc684xvmvquek9GthmFQvAKkorQ%3D&url=https%3A%2F%2Fakismet.com%2Ftos%2F)
    * ConvertKithis service is used for delivery of email updates and newsletters. We store your name and email address for purposes of delivering such communications.  Please refer to ConvertKit’s privacy policy for further information.
      * Newsletters: On the Website, you may subscribe to our newsletter, which may be used for advertising purposes. All newsletters sent may contain tracking pixels. The pixel is embedded in emails and allows an analysis of the success of online marketing campaigns. Because of these tracking pixels, we may see if and when you open an email and which links within the email you click. Also, this allows the Website to adapt the content of future newsletters to the interests of the user. This behavior will not be passed on to third parties.

At this time, your personal information is not shared with any other third-party applications. This list may be amended from time to time in the Website’s sole discretion.

Except when required by law, we will not sell, distribute, or reveal your email addresses or other personal information without your consent; however, we may disclose or transfer personal information collected through the Website to third parties who acquire all or a portion of our business, which may be the result of a merger, consolidation, or purchase of all or a portion of our assets, or in connection with any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding brought by or against us.

Please contact the developer for additional questions on the privacy policy. You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of our site.

Last updated: May 2, 2018.
